{
    "id": "acc3ed2e92144af2b01d134e5ac8aa8d",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is partial ………………….. his relatives.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "His infatuation ………………. her led him astray.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have great respect ………………….. him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is not qualified ………………….. the post.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Illiteracy is a hindrance …………………. progress.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There are several benefits …………………. traveling alone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He neither said nor did anything derogatory ………….………….. his position.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is desirous …………………. going abroad.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "of",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is respectful ………………… his senior officers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He has no prejudice ………………….. foreigners.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "against",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}